OPENING CREDITS
A Film by Director Name
INT. LIVING ROOM - DAY
JOHN enters the room quietly.
JOHN
(whispering)
Is anyone home?
The house is eerily silent.
Only the clock ticks.
MARY (O.S.)
John? Is that you?
JOHN
Yeah, it's me.
Where are you?
MARY enters from the kitchen,
wiping her hands on a towel.
MARY
I was making dinner.
How was your day?
JOHN
Long. Really long.
I need to tell you something.
MARY
(concerned)
What is it?
JOHN
I got the promotion.
MARY
(excited)
Oh my God! Really?
JOHN
Really. We're moving to New York.
MARY
(pause)
When?
JOHN
Next month.
Mary sits down heavily.
MARY
Next month? But what about...
JOHN
What about what?
MARY
Everything. Our life here.
JOHN
This is our future, Mary.
Our chance.
MARY
I know, but...
The conversation continues...
FADE TO BLACK.
END OF SCENE 1