Normal subtitle here.
Colored text with size
Multiple
lines
with   extra    spaces
HTML entities: &amp; &lt; &gt; &quot; &#39; &copy; &trade;
Overlapping bold and italic text
alert('xss')Dangerous contentbody
Unclosed tags bold italic
CSS injection: Test
Very long subtitle that might cause issues with rendering or processing when the text is extremely long and contains multiple sentences that could potentially break formatting or cause performance problems in some subtitle players or editors that don't handle long text well.
Special chars: café naïve résumé piñata 北京 عربي русский
Empty lines and malformed timestamp below:
00:34,000 -> 00:00:37,000
Malformed timestamp arrow
Normal ending.